examsplanner.in 2018-09-10

# Exams Planner – Privacy Policy

At Exams Planner, we respect the online privacy of our users and keep 'Personal Information' confidential. 'Personal Information' refers to information that can be used to identify any individual. It includes (but not limited to) first name, last name, residential address, email address or any other contact information (including that of home or work.) Speaking otherwise, you can access our website without disclosing any Personal Information.

Let's have a detailed look on our privacy policy as you are supposed to adhere to it as soon as you enter the website.

We collect two types of information from our users; personal and non-personal. Personal information includes name, gender, email address, postal address and phone number. Users are always free to share their personal information.

Non-personal information includes browser name, IP address, operating system, internet service provider and devices used to access the website.

#### We may use Cookies or other Technologies for tracking the user activities

_FYI, cookies are little text files, which save your personal information for session management. We neither save your password nor forward it to third party. However, it's your responsibility to avoid the settings for cookies, which may serve as platform for advertisement to capture your personal detail. Though, in any case you can use our website without worries._

#### You are the writer and the editor of your personal account!

_Undoubtedly, you have complete authority to access and change your name, password, and other details anywhere, anytime. Nobody else can access, modify, or delete your personal information._

## Privacy Policy Changes

Exams Planner reserves the rights to modify its Privacy Policy anytime. The changes come in effect from the day they appear on the website. So, visit this page frequently to stay updated.

## Disclaimer

We are only providing information regarding competitive exams and their schedule. If due to any reasons the exams get postponed or cancelled, we are not responsible. However, we will provide the update notifying such an event. The details of colleges are latest to the best of our knowledge. However, Exams Planner is not responsible for any changes in the course structure, duration, and fees. You should contact with the respective institution for any issues.

## Contact Us

_Email us or call us for all the queries for safety measures as well as services on offer! We feel proud to inform you about the exams and its impact on your future! Stays connected and share our vision to become the first to start your new career!_
